A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Associates, Fred Smith FA1225
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hawaiian Civic Projects, 1974-1979; 11; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - Hawaiian Civic and Related Projects I, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 211-212)
    Folder 211 - Part 1 of Volume I (#1-29); Folder 212 - Part 2 of Volume I (#30-88)
  - Hawaiian Civic and Related Projects, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 213-214)
    Folder 213 - Part 1 of Volume II (#89-124); Folder 214 - Part 2 of Volume II (#125-145)
  - Hawaiian Civic and Related Projects, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 215)
    Folder 215 - Volume III (#146-157)
- Paul Maze Book, 1958-1985; 12; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  Series 12 includes correspondence concerning a biography of the artist Paul Maze, with whom Laurance Rockefeller had become friends. The book, written by Anne Singer and entitled "Paul Maze: The Lost Impressionist", was published by Mr. Rockefeller.
  - Excerpts from Maze Correspondence: Fred Smith Notes, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 216)
  - Copies Sent, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 217)
  - Acknowledgements, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 218)
  - Reviews, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 219)
  - Fred Smith Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 220)
  - Mailing (Post Office), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 221)
  - Publishing (Aurum), Distribution (Kampmann), Promotion (Kaufman), 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 222)
  - Kampmann and Company: Inventory and Sales Analysis Reports, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 223)
  - Catalogues and Exhibitions, 1958, 1964, 1967, 1972, 1973, 1977, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 224)
- Princeton University, 1951-1991; 13; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  Series 13 contains material concerning Princeton University, Laurance Rockefeller's alma mater, particularly the establishment of Princeton's Center for Human Values in 1990.
  - Dedication of John D. Rockefeller 3rd College, October 16, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 225)
  - A Proposal for the Redesign of Princeton's Front Campus Entrance and the Creation of Stockton Court, February 1985 (Box 31, Folder 226)
  - President Harold T. Shapiro, 1988-1990 (Box 31, Folder 227-231)
    Folder 227 - Inaugural Address, January 8, 1988; Folder 228 - Commencement Address, June 7, 1988; Folder 229 - General (1989); Folder 230 - Commencement Remarks, June 12, 1990; Folder 231 - Opening Exercises, September 16, 1990
  - Proposal for Center for Human Values as Outlined by LSR and EJM, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 232)
  - Center for Human Values: Laurance S. Rockefeller Folder of Papers, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 233)
  - Center for Human Values: Prepared Press Release, 1990 June 26 (Box 32, Folder 234)
  - Center for Human Values: Press Conference, 1990 September 27 (Box 32, Folder 235)
  - Center for Human Values: Letters to Laurance S. Rockefeller and Responses, 1951, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 236)
  - Center for Human Values: Press Releases, Various, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 237)
  - Center for Human Values: Letters of Congratulation to Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 238, Box 33, Folder 239-240)
    Folder 238 - A-K; Folder 239 - L-Z; Folder 240 - Thank You Letters for LSR Signature
  - President Shapiro and Faculty Panel at Woodrow Wilson Award Ceremony for Laurance S. Rockefeller, February 16, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 241)
    - President Shapiro and Faculty Panel at Woodrow Wilson Award Ceremony for Laurance S. Rockefeller, Princeton University, February 16, 1991, 2017:FA1225:003 (Box 33, Folder 241)
- Rockefeller Family, 1963-1994; 14; 0.57 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box and 1 half-letter document box
  - David Rockefeller, 1969, 1971, 1977, 1978, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 242)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Conference and Celebration: Speeches and David Hamburg's Remarks, October 26-28, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 243)
  - "John D. Rockefeller, Jr. - Road Builder and Landscape Artist": An Intimate Look at His Role in the Development of the Carriage Roads at Acadia National Park, by Ann B. Roberts, 1988 June (Box 33, Folder 244)
  - "Moving Mountains", John D. Rockefeller Jr.'s Creation of Ideal Landscapes, by Chris Stacey, 1992 April 20 (Box 33, Folder 245)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1968, 1970, 1972, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 246)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1965-1966, 1973, 1978, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 247)
  - Press Clippings re Nelson A. Rockefeller's Vice Presidential Confirmation Hearings, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 248)
  - Public Relations Conference, 1965, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 249)
  - Rockefeller Family Archives - RG2 - Educational, Cultural and Business Interests: Material to Rockefeller Archive Center, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 250)
  - LOOK Magazine: "The Rockefellers' New York", 1963 March 26 (Box 34, Folder 251)
  - Bernice Kert: "Abby Aldrich Rockefeller: The Woman in the Family": Reviews, 1985-1986, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 252)